hey everybody talking one-on-one here in
this video is every single bankai in the
belief series who does it and a fun fact
about it alright ready let's go this is
the tensa zangetsu umbrella why do I
have this cuz it's awesome first
division the former head captain of the
gotei 13 sheera Ketchikan Ryu sy
Yamamoto his bankai is Zanka no tachi it
is arguably the strongest bankai in the
entire series as Yamamoto himself is
over 1,000 years old it is broken into
four different parts sonken Itachi east
west south and north it's not good on
tachi east compresses all the flames
from his shikai down to a single
longsword
anything that he cuts with his sword is
immediately incinerated out of existence
Zanka no tachi west compresses all the
flames around him making his body
temperature increased to over one
hundred and fifteen million degrees
Fahrenheit that's hotter than the
surface of the Sun nobody can even get
close to him while he has long gone
Itachi West activated as for Zanka no
tachi south it is arguably the most
badass technique in all of Bleach
Yamamoto rises the dead
the former enemies everybody he's slayed
by his swords in over the thousand years
in existence and they come back as
burning charred skeletons that are
basically his puppets he can control
them as he would his regular sword and
then finally Zanka no tachi north is
basically just a massive fuck off attack
that just incinerates everything more
than Zanka no tachi Ystad yeah a fun
fact about Yama's bankai is that it is
now in the possession a you ha bark
although he hasn't used it yet and some
people are wondering if he ever is going
to but moving on the former lieutenant
of the first division Choji no Sasaki
Bey's bankai is Tokyo gonorrheal Riku
it's lightning based it summons a
massive lightning dome behind him with
lightning bolts striking out of it and
he can basically just freely manipulate
and strike up wherever he wants with the
lightning bolt however he's never been
shown actually using it because it was
stolen by Driscoll Bercy and it was used
on Yamamoto a fun fact about this is
that he's never actually used it in
battle before even though he's mastered
it - please Yamamoto and when Yamamoto
was attacked by a by Driscoll he stated
that the bankai that shojiro had was not
this week so arguably when shojiro was
using it properly it was a lot stronger
now the current captain commander of the
gotei 13 and former captain of the 8th
division students week yaku's bankai is
conten kyokotsu Korematsu Shinju it's
able to manipulate
the entire battlefield converting it
into stages of a play referred to as
Dawn's depending on which dawn that
students we is in the entire battlefield
warps this is not an illusion this is
not just mentioning messing with the
person's mind this is physically
changing the area around to suit his
needs the first dawn conflict' all the
injuries that you should sui has endured
on to his opponent the second dawn
causes a disease to spread on the
opponent's body
the third dawn summons in a massive
underwater area where they'll both drown
and the fourth dawn causes the
opponent's head to be sliced off and
then subsequently blown up by a thread
that he has fun fact about this is that
his bankai also summons is a zanpakuto
spirit and kyokotsu behind it which
takes the form of two women now this is
indicating as soon suiza
relationship with his zanpakuto is a
little bit more intimate and romantic if
you know what I mean
second division captain SOI fons bankai
chuckle all right Obon is a massive fuck
off missile yeah I mean I hate her
character but damn that's cool her
bankai basically converts it into a
giant really heavy missile on her arm
although SOI fon hates to use it because
it basically goes against her pride as
the captain of the assassination corpse
it's way too big to move and it's way
too flashy - you know assassinate
somebody from a distance but man is it
cool fun fact is she can only use it
once every three days she can you know
use it more than that but it taxes her
considerably which just makes it be
known that SOI phone has quite the
considerable amount of stamina their
third division ex captain Guinea -
maru's bankai , she Nino yari basically
just extends the shikai ability whereas
the Shi Kai could extend the sword 100
swords length the bankai can extend it
indefinitely we don't actually know how
far it can extend GG instead it was
about 13 kilometers but that was
revealed to later be a lie and he also
said they can travel really fast beyond
the speed of sound but that was also
revealed to be alive the only thing we
know for certain is it's really fucking
long and it's really fucking fast the
true ability of his bankai though is
whenever it's extending and contracting
he can leave a little sliver of the
blade inside of the person and then he
can activate the true bankai ability
kill commission no yari which allows
heavy whatever area is being afflicted
by the sword to be disintegrated on a
cellular level a fun fact about this is
that he attempted to use this against
Aizen but it didn't really work not
really a fun fact cuz he died but that's
all
got another former captain of the 3rd
division and somebody you probably don't
even remember cuz it was any anime only
arc is shusuke amagai and his bankai was
hold on I have to read this here um
right get going Kaku yeah no one
remembers this
it's a giant seashell that spits fire
that's that's pretty much it the current
captain of the 3rd division if he's not
dead which he might possibly be Roger Oh
Otonashi or just rose is king shahdov
butoden it summons an entire dance
troupe that's able to being manipulated
by roses conductors one basically his
bankai takes the form of a concert of
the different stages of a concert
similar to shewn squeeze which was a
play the first act of the plane we don't
know if this is the only things he can
do with his bankai possibly he can do a
lot more with it but the ones that we
saw were the following act one Seadrift
manipulating sound to make it seem like
an entire whirlpools around the opponent
act 2 Prometheus using the same sound
based abilities he's able to summon
shine fireballs to burn the opponent and
finally act 3 um the hero's journey was
never seen because he was kind of killed
by massed a mass Julian before he had a
chance to but once again we don't really
know his bankai
could do more than that fun fact is that
he's actually manipulating his opponents
a sense of sound so even though it looks
like fire and water it's not really that
it's just that the opponent is being
manipulated to the point that he feels
that he's being attacked by water or by
fire
former 4th division captain Rhett Seward
shooter who Nahanni the first kampachi
spawn kai is mean uzuki and we honestly
don't know really what this can do some
people say it's blood some people say
it's acid but yeah just summons a bunch
of goop behind her and she was killed by
Kenpachi before we actually got to see
what it could truly do um but it is kind
of freaky um fun fact about it is that
her shikai and bankai actually say uh
share the same name on mean uzuki it's
just a different translation for each
one can we move on please this is really
getting uncomfortable 6 division captain
byakuya kuchiki bankai is senbonzakura
kageyoshi
it can also extend the aspects of his
shikai whereas the shikai can only
create 1000 flower petals this has
multiplied over to hundreds of millions
in senbonzakura kageyoshi he can also
redirect the the petals using his hands
making them twice as fast and
a variety of techniques he can create
using these flower petals sink' the
massacre scene compresses all the
individual flower petals down into an
array of blades that he can summon
whenever he desires go Kay creates an
entire sphere of the swirling mass of
razor blades that he can compress on the
opponent killing them immediately and
then his final finishing move
Shu K Haku taken compresses all the
flower petals down to a single blade
with a Kip hair of kick-ass angel wings
for one final attack fun fact is it may
or may not have gone stronger ever since
he's been training at the soul house so
we're just gonna have to wait and see
the lieutenant of the six division Renji
a bar I actually has two forms of his
bankai the first form that were made
aware of his he he owes aa BIMARU which
creates a massive snake attachment that
he controls kind of like a whip his
special technique in this form was he
cuts through tae-ho which basically just
compresses all of his reiatsu together
into one big attack he can also separate
the joints in order to dispel certain
attacks from the opponent however this
was later revealed only to be half of
his bankai as full potential by each
ebay heosu Bey who revealed that his
zanpakuto is not really lying to him
just kind of you know holding back the
true power until he was ready but after
he did become ready after he trained at
the soul house Ichi Bay told him the
true name of his bankai Soul zombie Maru
taking full advantage of both the snake
and the baboon aspect now he can control
an entire Pabu arm on his left side so
you know event rate increasing punching
power and then the sword on his right
side can be freely manipulated in
different shapes and forms relating a
new technique he owes a coup which is
basically an attack that bites down the
opponent using the snake aspect and I
don't know burns them to a cinder as
we've seen with masked a masculine it's
a really cool bonk I hope we see it
again later 7th division captain such
income amorous bankai is kokujo tengen
me all it creates a giant that is
completely manipulated by comum or
whatever movements he makes the giant
makes a downside to this though is that
every attack that the giant endures soda
sahjhan however a reverse of this is
that whenever sahjhan heals his bankai
heals as well he is the only known
bankai that is able to repair itself
usually every other bankai if it gets
damaged it's gone forever as we've seen
with ichigo's tensa zangetsu fun fact
about this is that after he mastered the
humanization technique from his
shit lost clan he was able to activate
Coco choten get me all Don guy Joe
shedding the armor so it's just a
complete massive REO however now the co
more has been turning to well a dog we
don't really know if he's gonna be able
to use bankai again or what form that
would take just keep in mind at the
moment there is nobody in the 8th
division and those bankai because soon
Sui was moved over to the first division
so moving on to the 9th division we have
the current captain who also probably is
most likely dead kin say mu Karuma his
bankai is Tekken touchy Kazi compressing
his sword down to two gauntlets on his
right and left arm as well as this giant
stretchy thing that's behind him don't
really know what's up with that but
anyway he can control the shape of these
gauntlets on his arm he's made them axe
blades he's made them like brass
knuckles before and every time he comes
in contact with something as long as
he's in contact with the blade touching
the opponent as successive explosions
will be set off basically nuking the
opponent out of existence a interesting
fun fact here with Ken say as he was the
first visor to release his bankai now
the former captain of the 9th division
Kaname Tosen spawn Chi is suzumushi
shush-shush key and makoto key whilst
inside this black dome the senses of
sight hearing and smell are removed from
the opponent allowing Kaname to attack
his will with his sealed zanpakuto
however it doesn't take away the sense
of touch which is a fun fact
ah well fun fact for me not so much
anybody that could figure out really
quickly how his bankai works as did
kampachi and he was eliminated also once
he activated his Hall as I holla
fication we don't really know if he can
use bankai or if it would be different
and we won't in the future because well
he's dead 10th division captain toshiro
hitsugaya Steiger and Yuri Maru it's one
that's also just an extension of his
shikai it creates massive ice swings as
long as ice up and down his body ending
in a sword he's able to use an array of
icy techniques as long with the most
basic and probably the most strongest
technique of whether subjugation he's
able to manipulate snow and rain and
frost at will this will lead to his most
strongest technique joltin caucus oh and
a fun fact here is that his bankai is
probably the least difference between
the shikai and into the bankai state
he's able to use technically any
technique in his bankai in his shikai
and vice versa it's just that when he
ever uses the bigger techniques like ryu
Senka and heal
and Yaka so well and shikai it's just a
lot more dangerous and also he might be
kind of an experienced he's trying to
train up to learn his bankai but we
don't really know he's mastered it yet
the ice flowers represent how long he
has left in his bankai and I'm gonna
assume that whatever the ice flowers are
just gone and he's allowed to stay in
his bankai indefinitely that's when he's
truly mastered it and he hasn't reached
that point yet so keep on training
Toshiro or not I really don't care I
don't really like to show that much 11th
division captain Kenpachi Zaraki spawn
Kai is unknown we don't know the name
because it was just revealed in the last
bleach chapter 669 it turns him into a
ochre oni Kishin sort of deal it removes
all sense of individuality or reason or
speech rhyme and he just turns into a
massive guts beserker lunatic attacking
his opponent which a much more shrunken
down form of nose Arashi fun fact about
this is it's the only bankai in
existence that operates in this way
actually changing the person's
personality that activates it we don't
really know what's up with it yet we do
know yet series involved a little bit
who is most likely the true form of nose
Arashi but as I said it was just
revealed in the last chapter so we don't
really know much about it yet the third
seat of the 11th division II Kaku Madara
Mays bankai is Ryu mo Hazuki Maru it
takes the three segments from his shikai
and makes them into basically just three
massive fuck-off weapons two blades that
he's holding as well as a giant uh I
don't know what the Japanese name for
that thing is you'll probably tell me in
the comments but anyway yeah his bankai
is essentially just a huge mass of power
but that's not necessarily a good thing
because it means that there's no speed
and no defense just using it once in his
fight against edaradi Lyonnaise arrancar
number 13 he managed to damage it
considerably and although Alcon was able
to kind of piece it back together
superficially as I stated once the
bankai is broken
there ain't no repairing that shit so
REO Mon hazuki motto is not even close
to being as strong as it originally was
a fun fact is that he coffee was on
Pocket Oh spirit hozukimaru is a kind of
a lazy open takes a long-ass time waking
up when you cock he goes into bankai you
can keep the progress monitored on this
on a blade and whenever that dragon is
fully lit up in crimson red well you
better watch out or ever you're fighting
against because he cock who's about to
bust out some good old-fashioned 11
squad ass-whooping on ya
yeah 12th division captain my Yuri could
cinchy his bankai is konjiki ashisogi
jizo creating a massive um I don't even
know what this thing is it's a
caterpillar baby bladed things whatever
it shoots poison the poison can be
modified by my Yuri at will it's made of
his own blood so he's not affected by it
neither is nemu his assistant captain
and his bankai is probably the most
versatile because him being a mad
scientist he's rigged it to explode in
case it's ever used against him and he
used the demon womb raft and disease to
further its evolution into a giant baby
wearing a loin cloth um whatever attack
or technique that the enemy uses against
the demon wound wrapped in disease will
be able to be simulated by it and then
the giant baby will give birth to
another giant baby by a c-section
that is completely modified in immune to
whatever technique it learned from the
opponent okay can we move on I mean my
yard is my favorite captain but man this
is kind of disturbing yeah little bit
the former captain of the 12th division
and current awesome candy shop owner
quisqueya Haris bankai is Kenan Brockie
bene he may at arome i probably
pronounced that wrong but whatever it
summons a giant woman behind him and
he's able to freely reconstruct and
reconstitute whatever he desires with
his bankai this includes our repairing
his eyes that were completely destroyed
by asking or remodel fiying his arm to
make it more stronger or to basically
allow other people in this certain field
that was apparently
inescapable by asking he was able to
penetrate it all in all it's not really
a bankai that's known for attacking it's
more restructuring but the things you
can do with it are possibly endless
especially since you are Hara is a
genius we didn't really get to see that
much of it as with chem Pacis but it is
pretty kick-ass fun fact about it is
that he attained this bankai the same
way that Ichigo did by using the
three-day method with the 10-sheet eye
it was kind of dangerous to do but it so
hard we're talking about here so that
guy pulled it off 13th division
lieutenant Rukia Kuchiki and my favorite
bleach characters bankai is Hakka no
toga make it completely encases her in
ice making her Chi like an ice statue
which also kinda makes me question if
she can even move while she's in this
bankai and from what we've seen of it
basically just sets off an atom bomb of
cold around her anything that's even
close to her gets frozen to the very
bony core and just disintegrates into
the wind
we gonna say that her bankai is one of
the very few her like a one-hit ko cuz
like I said it doesn't look like she can
really fight while in that state and
even the act of releasing her bankai and
going back to her shikai stage or her
silva state it takes a lot of effort if
you make one misstep you're screwed over
so I'm gonna say it's the one-hit ko
iced bankai and now finally those zero
divisions captain each of a heosu be his
bankai is ichimonji Sheriff Uday it's
not really called a bankai though he
refers it to us like the evolution of a
zanpakuto because his is quite possibly
the very first zanpakuto ever in
creation I transforms his a black pan
into a white pen and whenever he attacks
with he's able to rename whatever he
strikes so in his shikai he blots out
whatever it is and then in his bankai he
can rename it and whatever he renames it
as will have the same qualities as that
for example when he used it against you
ah he renamed him black and so whatever
abilities or power that you all had has
now been reduced to just the power of a
black hand which is like a feeble little
insect that each EBA thought he could
just smash with his hands of course you
are as freaking you high and that didn't
really go out too well but there you go
ladies and gentlemen that's every
fucking bankai and bleach god my mouth
is ah I mean I gotta go get a drink
anyway I hope you guys enjoyed I think I
got them all I think pretty sure I know
someone's gonna comment like you forgot
about this trivial character that nobody
cares about but it's okay
alright everybody say a techie signing
out
okay okay okay okay I was just seeing to
say I want to see how many people are
actually gonna comment take you for God
I'm like oh man you guys are funny all
right here we go
ichigo kurosaki main character the
series bankai tensa zangetsu we don't
actually know what the current tensa
zangetsu looks like as he hasn't used it
yet after it was reforged me my Bonnie
Maya but his original bankai was pretty
simple it just compressed down all the
power into a cloak and his sword and he
was able to launch black hits again ten
shows a little bit more powerful the
cloak was part of his bankai I guess
I'll make that the fun fact and you can
basically measure how much spiritual
energy he has left based on how much of
the cloak is still there this bankai was
also shared by shiro ichigo or the
hollow inside of ichigo before we found
out what's up with that and it was
basically the same exact thing except uh
swapped color schemes there um yeah
ichigo's bankai not really that
interesting honestly is not as elaborate
I guess I should say as the others oh it
also gave him super speed which that
kind of became trivial after a while to
remember that remember when he first
went bankai against pyaar kiya any speed
blitz the fuck out of him it's like whoa
ichigo's wicked fast now and then after
that like every other opponent he's
fought against the speed wasn't really
like okay you're at least you're pretty
faster on par with me I guess I guess
gives you a decent decent speed I guess
maybe possibly unless you're houki aura
alright anyway hope you guys enjoyed the
video um I might be making a video in
the future about all the different star
riders and their volt standings or at
least they're different individual
powers cuz we know all of them I'll
leave a comment below on what you think
and what is your favorite bankai hope
you enjoyed teching signing out
you